<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security on Nick's Blog</title><link>https://ruffles.dev/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on Nick's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ruffles.dev/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Upgrading a Kubernetes Cluster</title><link>https://ruffles.dev/posts/cluster_upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ruffles.dev/posts/cluster_upgrade/</guid><description>Upgrading the controlplane node On the controlplane node, run the following commands:
This will update the package lists from the software repository.
apt update # This will install the kubeadm version 1.24.0 apt-get install kubeadm=1.24.0-00 # Show the possible upgrades you can do kubeadm upgrade plan # This will upgrade Kubernetes controlplane node. kubeadm upgrade apply v1.24.0 # This will update the kubelet with the version 1.24.0. apt-get install kubelet=1.24.0-00 # You may need to reload the daemon and restart kubelet service after it has been upgraded.</description></item><item><title>YubiKey 5C commit signing and SSH authentication</title><link>https://ruffles.dev/posts/yubikey/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ruffles.dev/posts/yubikey/</guid><description>While being onboarded to my new job at EngineerBetter, I was handed a YubiKey and asked to set it up with SSH authentication and commit signing. While I had heard of GPG and used it slightly before, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t aware that you could also use it in git to sign your commits in order to prove that you were the one to commit code.
The setup for my YubiKey took me about a day, as there was issue after issue with the YubiKey, so in this guide I hope to show a relatively painless and secure setup for the YubiKey.</description></item></channel></rss>